{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Try to guess these Pixar characters.",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "WALL-E",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "The helpful post-war robot"
  }, {
    "answer": "Dory",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Friendly blue fish with short-term memory loss"
  }, {
    "answer": "Nemo",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Clownfish who lives in a dentist's aquarium"
  }, {
    "answer": "Sheriff Woody",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Cowboy doll who is devoted to his owner, Andy"
  }, {
    "answer": "Buzz Lightyear",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Space Ranger from Starfleet Command"
  }, {
    "answer": "Mike Wazowski",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Round green monster with a Medusa-like girlfriend"
  }, {
    "answer": "James P. Sullivan",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "The leading scarer, but not very scary"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bob Parr/Mr. Incredible",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Retired superhero who becomes an insurance adjuster"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lightning McQueen",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Red sports car who wants to win the Piston Cup"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jessie",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Cowgirl doll who doesn't want to go back into the dark"
  }, {
    "answer": "Mater",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Rusty old (but good-natured) pick-up truck"
  }, {
    "answer": "Helen Parr/Elastigirl",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Superhero -- and mother of three other superheroes"
  }, {
    "answer": "Frozone",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Superhero who can freeze things in an instant"
  }, {
    "answer": "Remy",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "The rodent who became a chef"
  }, {
    "answer": "Buddy Pine/Syndrome",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Wannabe superhero who terrorizes superheroes"
  }, {
    "answer": "Carl Fredericksen",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Feisty old man who flies his house to Paradise Falls"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hopper",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Grasshopper who intimidates the ant colony"
  }, {
    "answer": "Flik",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Ant who wants to make a difference for his colony"
  }, {
    "answer": "Stinky Pete",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Prospector doll who wants to move to Japan"
  }, {
    "answer": "Henry J. Waternoose",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Owns a factory that produces electricity from screams"
  }, {
    "answer": "Alfredo Linguini",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "the son of Auguste Gusteau"
  }, {
    "answer": "Luxo Jr.",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Pixar mascot"
  }, {
    "answer": "Pizza Planet",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "The pizza place that Andy takes woody to"
  }, {
    "answer": "Russell",
    "category": "Pixar Characters",
    "question": "Wilderness Explorer who is trying to earn merit badges"
  }],
  "quizLength": 1,
  "title": "Pixar Characters",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/user-quizzes/23069/pixar-characters-quiz"
}
